# ADIYANSAH S.KOM

Tambun Selatan, Bekasi Phone: +6287741413213

Email: adiyansahcode@gmail.com

Web: www.adiyansahcode.id



### About Me

I am a Web Developer. I have become a web developer since 2014. At the beginning of my career i use Codeigniter in my project, then I use the PHP Phalcon, Laravel, Lumen and I also used the Java Spring in my project. and now I'm focussed on the backend developer who use Restful API.

# Skill & Expertise

PHP Developer:

JavaScript Developer:

Backend Developer:

Database Analyst:

System Analyst:

Sysadmin:

# Work Experience

Web Developer on PT. Prima Tangguh Abadi

October 2015 - March 2016

Analyze and creating a ERP system with Codeigniter and SQL Server.

Web Developer on PT. Loka Citra Media

April 2016 - July 2018

Analyze and creating Web-Base system with Codeigniter and MySQL.

Backend Developer on PT. Sigma Cipta Caraka

August 2018 - August 2021

Analyze and creating RESTful API Services with PHP Phalcon, PHP Lumen and Java Spring.

Web Developer on PT. Ekomoditi Solutions Indonesia

September 2021 – Present

Analyze and creating Web-Base system and RESTful API Services with Yii, Laravel and MySQL.

### Education

AMIK BINA SARANA INFORMATIKA, BEKASI

Manajemen Informatika D3 2011 - 2014

STMIK NUSA MANDIRI, JAKARTA

Sistem Informasi S1 2014 - 2015

## **PORTOFOLIO**

#### 1. Project Link2bos.com



Owner: PT. BAE Orbit Senusantara

Role : WEB Developer (PHP Codeigniter)

Year : 2018

#### 2. Project IbosAcademy.com



Owner: PT. BAE Orbit Senusantara

Role : WEB Developer (PHP Codeigniter)

Year : 2018

#### 3. Project Hirest



#### HOTEL IN ROOM SERVICE & RESERVATION

Owner: TelkomSigma

Role : Backend Developer (PHP Phalcon)

Year : 2018

#### Project MBike



Owner: TelkomSigma

Role : Backend Developer (Java Spring)

Year : 2019

#### 5. Project NSAM Enhancement and BroFist



Owner: Telkomsel

Role : Backend Developer (PHP Phalcon)

Year : 2019

#### 6. Project NRA



Owner: Telkomsel

Role : Data Analysis (Power BI)

Year : 2020

#### 7. Project Iriis



Owner: Telkomsel

Role : Backend Developer (PHP Phalcon)

Year : 2020

#### 8. Project Etha



Owner: Bank DKI

Role : WEB Developer (Laravel)

Year : 2020

#### 9. Project Trans Shopping Mall



Owner: Trans Corp

Role : Backend Developer (PHP Lumen)

Year : 2021